MAYURESH BAILURKAR

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER









https://mayureshbailurkar.github.io/

0

https://github.com/MAYURESHBAILURKAR

≅ ⊢

+91-7019021346

 \vee

mayureshbailurkar@gmail.com

0

Belgaum, Karnataka

SKILLS

- React.JS, Redux, CSS, Javascript, Chakra UI, HTML5, Postman, Node.JS, Express.Js, Mongoose, and MongoDB
- Problem-Solving
- Data structure and Algorithm (DSA)
- GitHub

SOFT SKILL

- Online collaboration
- Adaptability
- Remote Work
- Team work

EDUCATION

MASAI SCHOOL

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

Apr-2022 - present

KLE ENGINEERING COLLEGE, BELGAUM

V.T.U

August -2014 - June 2018

GSS COLLEGE BELGAUM

PUC

August-2012 - May 2014

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCING - 3D Visualizer

Oct 2020 - Mar 2022

 Worked closely with designers to create visually appealing and accurate renders.

PARIKH AND ASSOCIATES - SANGLI

- 3D Visualizer

Dec 2019 - Jul 2020

- Create visual concepts, by hand or using computer software.
- Worked closely with designers to create visually appealing and accurate renders.

PROFILE

Excellent understanding of frontend and backend programming languages and technology stacks. Demonstrating creativity and analytical skills while completing development, testing, and debugging tasks. Worked with teams to design API and web architecture. Capable of writing production-ready code using ReactJS, Redux, and CSS on the frontend, NodeJS, and Express on the backend.

PROJECT

MYTHERESA.COM - MERN (CLONE) INDIVISUAL PROJECT

Features

- Designed and developed a user-friendly website basis client requirements.
- Designed back-end as well as front-end with optimum security.
- Backend MVC-based Architecture contains Users, products, and respective cart details.
- Designed Redux single flow of data and added Authentication, Search Bar, Sorting, and Filtering features for products.
- Used Stripe Payment Infrastructure for checkout.
- Developing and maintaining software solutions using SDLC standards and best practices.
- Used React Framework to make the platform accessible to screen readers for desktop and mobile web applications. Added responsive components for all screen sizes.

Tech-Stack

REACT JS | NODE JS | MONGODB | EXPRESS JS | JWT | REDUX | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | CHAKRA UI | HTML | STRIPE

SKINSTORE.COM (CLONE) O INDIVISUAL PROJECT

Features

- End-to-End product purchasing flow of the website.
- Login check with (reqres.in), Sorting, and Filtering features for products.
- Individual Project completed in 1 week.
- Displaying products added to the cart with details like price, size, quantity, etc.
- The functionality provided to increase the quantity of a product, and changes in price to be displayed under each product and subtotal.
- Executed the Project with pixel-perfect accuracy and provided important functionalities.
- Documented software development methodologies in technical manuals to be used by IT personnel in future projects.
- Added new components for the platform and completed all the CRs on time.
- Solved high-critical defects.

Tech-Stack

REACT JS | CSS | JAVASCRIPT | CHAKRA UI

HIVERH.COM (CLONE)



GROUP PROJECT

Features

- Used Advance CSS and Login check are provided.
- Completed Project in 1 week with a team of 5.

Area of Responsibility

- Was responsible for creating 3 service pages using HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- Executed the pages with pixel-perfect accuracy and functionality.

Tech-Stack

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT